const QuizData =
  [
    {
      Question: "What type of game is Valorant?",//1
      Choice: ["Battle Royale", "MOBA", "Tactical Shooter", "RPG"],
      Answer: "Tactical Shooter",
    },
    {
      Question: "Which company developed Valorant?",//2
      Choice: ["Blizzard Entertainment", "Riot Games", "Valve Corporation", "Epic Games"],
      Answer: "Riot Games",
    },
    {
      Question: "What is the maximum number of players in a single Valorant match?",//3
      Choice: ["8", "10", "12", "16"],
      Answer: "10",
    },
    {
      Question: "What is the primary objective in Valorantâ€™s standard game mode?",//4
      Choice: ["Capture the Flag", "Defuse the Bomb", "Destroy the Enemy Base", "Collect Resources"],
      Answer: "Defuse the Bomb",
    },
    {
      Question: "Which of the following is not a game mode in Valorant?",//5
      Choice: ["Deathmatch", "Spike Rush", "Domination", "Competitive"],
      Answer: "Domination",
    },
    {
      Question: "What is the in-game currency used to buy weapons and abilities in Valorant?",//6
      Choice: ["Gold", "Credits", "Coins", "Points"],
      Answer: "Credits",
    },
    {
      Question: "Which of these agents is known for their healing abilities?",//7
      Choice: ["Sage", "Jett", "Cypher", "Brimstone"],
      Answer: "Sage",
    },
    {
      Question: "In Valorant, what does the 'Ultimate' ability refer to?",//8
      Choice: ["A special weapon", "A powerful agent ability with a long cooldown", "A new game mode", "A type of map"],
      Answer: "A powerful agent ability with a long cooldown",
    },
    {
      Question: "Which map feature allows players to teleport across the map in Valorant?",//9
      Choice: ["Rifts", "Teleporters", "Portals", "Gates"],
      Answer: "Teleporters",
    },
    {
      Question: "What is the term for a player who excels in eliminating opponents and has high accuracy?",//10
      Choice: ["Tank", "Support", "Duelist", "Scout"],
      Answer: "Duelist",
    },
  ]
  export default QuizData;